import 'package:codekameleon/model/quiz_model.dart';

const List<QuizModel> cppQuizzes = [
  QuizModel(
      question: 'Who invented C++?',
      answer: 3,
      options: [
        'Dennis Ritchie',
        'Ken Thompson',
        'Brian Kernighan',
        'Bjarne Stroustrup'
      ],
  ),
  QuizModel(
      question: 'What is C++?',
      answer: 2,
      options: [
        'C++ is an object oriented programming language',
        'C++ is a procedural programming language',
        'C++ supports both procedural and object oriented programming language',
        'C++ is a functional programming language'
      ]
  ),
  QuizModel(
      question: 'Which of the following type is provided by C++ but not C?',
      answer: 3,
      options: [
        'double',
        'float',
        'int',
        'bool'
      ]
  ),
  QuizModel(
      question: 'What is the size of wchar_t in C++?',
      answer: 0,
      options: [
        'Based on the number of bits in the system',
        '2 or 4',
        '4',
        '2'
      ]
  ),
  QuizModel(
      question: 'Which is more effective while calling the C++ functions?',
      answer: 3,
      options: [
        'call by object',
        'call by pointer',
        'call by value',
        'call by reference'
      ]
  ),
  QuizModel(
      question: 'Which of the following is used to terminate the function declaration in C++?',
      answer: 0,
      options: [
        ';',
        ']',
        ')',
        ':'
      ]
  ),
  QuizModel(
      question: 'Which keyword is used to define the macros in c++?',
      answer: 1,
      options: [
        '#macro',
        '#define',
        'macro',
        'define'
      ]
  ),
  QuizModel(
      question: 'The C++ code which causes abnormal termination/behaviour of a program should be written under _________ block.',
      answer: 2,
      options: [
        'catch',
        'throw',
        'try',
        'finally'
      ]
  ),
  QuizModel(
      question: 'What is Inheritance in C++?',
      answer: 0,
      options: [
        'Deriving new classes from existing classes',
        'Overloading of classes',
        'Classes with same names',
        'Wrapping of data into a single class'
      ]
  ),
  QuizModel(
      question: 'What is meant by a polymorphism in C++?',
      answer: 2,
      options: [
        'class having only single form',
        'class having four forms',
        'class having many forms',
        'class having two forms'
      ]
  ),
];
